FRANK CHAU

1823 FLEMING ST. POMONA, CA 91766

626-217-6718 • frankchau93@gmail.com • www.linkedin.com/in/frankchau

OBJECTIVE

Highly motivated undergraduate student with experience in developing websites, programming and using SQL language seeks an internship or job opportunity in web development, back-end database management and Information Technology to leverage existing skills and gain experience.

EDUCATION

CALIFORNIA POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY, POMONA

GPA: 3.71

Bachelor of Science, Computer Information Systems

EXPECTED: JUNE 2015

RELATED COURSEWORK: Interactive Web Development, E-Commerce Application Development, Multimedia applications on the Web, Database Design & Development.

EXPERIENCE

I&IT WEB DEVELOPMENT

POMONA, CA 2014-PRESENT

POMONA, CA

- Maintained and updated various websites from various organizations within the campus.
- Enforced web standards so that users can have a positive web browsing experience.
- Converted old campus websites to a new, clean Bootstrap framework so all websites are responsive and compliant.

XSERV CONSULTING CORP.

CHINO HILLS, CA

2011-2014

- Developed a real estate website for a client which gave them an opportunity for them to advertise their history, accomplishments, and services.
- Utilized ASP.NET web forms in order to build dynamic online reports for management to keep track of inventory.
- Refined various FoxPro reports to reflect the client's business models.
- Created multiple functions in different FoxPro programs to meet the client's current needs and increase productivity.
- Modified FoxPro reports for a client to include more sorting options and organized structure in order to produce effective data that the client needs.

SKILLS

- Operating Systems Windows 98/2000/XP/7/8, Ubuntu
- Web Development HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Cascade CMS
- Programming ASP.NET Web Forms, ASP.NET MVC, Python, Java, C#, Visual FoxPro
- Microsoft Office Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access
- Database SQL Server 2012, Visual Foxpro
- App Development Windows 8

HONORS AND REWARDS

- Dean's list from Fall Quarter 2011 to Winter Quarter 2014, Cal Poly Pomona
- Principal's Honor List for "Exceptional Academic Standing", 2011-2012, Cal Poly Pomona